http://www.marsair.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Mars Air Systems LLC Privacy Policy14716 S. BroadwayGardena, CA. 90248 Your privacy is very important to us. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect and share information and data when you use the Mars Air Systems website (the “Site”) and otherwise share Personal Information with Mars Air Systems. This Privacy Policy also explains your choices for managing your information preferences, including opting out of certain uses of your Personal Information. By using the Site you consent to this Privacy Policy. Managing Your Information PreferencesYou can always review, correct, update or delete your Personal Information from our records or opt out of receiving marketing e-mails from us by e-mailing us at privacyofficer@marsair.com Information We CollectPersonal InformationWe only collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, address, e-mail and other personally identifiable information that you choose to provide us with (“Personal Information”). For example, you may be required to provide us with certain Personal Information to register with the Site, to sign up for certain services available through the Site, to make a purchase and at other times.Usage DataWe may collect anonymous data about users of our Site (“Usage Data”). For example, each time you use the Site we may automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the pages you view and the time and duration of your visits to the Site. This anonymous information, however, does not identify any specific person. We use Usage Data to improve the quality of our Site.Cookies and Web BeaconsWe may use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and browser). We may also use Web beacons (an electronic file placed on a website that monitors usage). We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the experience of the Site. We do not use cookies or Web beacons to collect Personal Information. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Site may not work if you delete or disable cookies. How We Use Information and When We May Share InformationGeneralWe use Personal Information for internal purposes only, such as providing you with the Site and our products and services, having our sales representatives contact you regarding your product and service inquiries and to otherwise communicate with you about Mars Air Systems, the Site and our product and services. We will not disclose Personal Information to third parties without your consent, except as explained in this Privacy Policy.Service ProvidersFrom time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses that we believe trustworthy and who have confirmed that their privacy practices are consistent with ours (“Service Providers”). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as hosting, maintenance and other information technology services. We only provide our Service Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of theinformation involved, in order to protect Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified by us.Other TransfersWe may share Personal Information and Usage Data with businesses controlling, controlled by or under common control with Mars Air Systems. If Mars Air Systems is merged, acquired or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Usage Data in connection with such transaction. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if, in our discretion, the new entity plans to handle your information in a way that differs materially from this Privacy Policy.Compliance with Laws and Law EnforcementMars Air Systems cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information and any other information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it isnecessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of Mars Air Systems or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law. SecurityMars Air Systems recognizes the importance of safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. However, no data transmission over theInternet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Site, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site, and you do so at your own risk. Links to Other websitesOur Site may contain links to other websites, or allow others to send you such links. A link to a third party’s website does not mean that we endorse it or that we are affiliated with it. We do not exercise control over third-party websites. You access such third-party websites or content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party website before providing any information to the website. Your California Privacy RightsUnder California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship (1) a list of the categories of personal information, such as name, address, e-mail address, and the type of services provided to thatcustomer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, and (2) the names and addresses of all such third parties. To request the above information, please email the Privacy Officer at privacyofficer@marsair.com or write to us at: Mars Privacy OfficerMars Air Systems LLC14716 S. BroadwayGardena, CA. 90248 We will respond to such written requests within 30 days following receipt at the mailing address above. We reserve the right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified above or otherwise exempted by law. Please note that we are required only to respond to each customer once per calendar year. Children’s PrivacyThe Site is not directed at children. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. Privacy Policy ChangesFrom time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Those changes will go into effect on the Revision Date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site constitutes yourconsent to the revised Privacy Policy. To request additional information about our Privacy Policy please email the Privacy Officer at privacyofficer@marsair.com or write to us at: Mars Privacy OfficerMars Air Systems LLC14716 S. BroadwayGardena, CA. 90248Phone: 310-532-1555Revised: December 27, 2012
Privacy Policy
